{
    "Page": 1,
    "TotalPages": 1,
    "AnswerSets": [
        {
            "AnswerSetId": 7701627,
            "Created": "2010-12-21T09:05:16Z",
            "Completed": "2010-12-21T09:07:08Z",
            "Updated": "2010-12-21T09:07:08Z",
            "Survey": 24154,
            "Respondent": -1,
            "Answers": [
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660586,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:07:08Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390002,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "Name, Vorname",
                    "AnswerText": "Lenczyk, Astrid",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660587,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:07:08Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390003,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "Hochschule, Ort",
                    "AnswerText": "Westfälische-Wilhelms Universität",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660588,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:07:08Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390004,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "E-Mail-Adresse",
                    "AnswerText": "astrid.lenczyk@wiwi.uni-muenster.de",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660491,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:06:41Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390005,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "nein",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660425,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:06:17Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390010,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "ja",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660411,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:06:11Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390013,
                    "QuestionType": "DROPDOWN",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "jedes Wintersemester",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660387,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:06:04Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390024,
                    "QuestionType": "CHECKBOX",
                    "QuestionText": "(Mehrfachnennung möglich)",
                    "AnswerText": "",
                    "AnswerNumeric": -1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660388,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:06:10Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390024,
                    "QuestionType": "CHECKBOX",
                    "QuestionText": "Master",
                    "AnswerText": "",
                    "AnswerNumeric": -1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660371,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:06:01Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390028,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "Anzahl:",
                    "AnswerText": "50",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660364,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:05:55Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390031,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "Cases and Presentation",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660325,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:05:45Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390032,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "ja, als eines von mehreren Lehrbüchern",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660222,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:05:26Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390037,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "gut",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 100660196,
                    "Created": "2010-12-21T09:05:21Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 7701627,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390042,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "gut",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "AnswerSetId": 19509338,
            "Created": "2012-02-23T11:30:03Z",
            "Completed": "2012-02-23T11:34:06Z",
            "Updated": "2012-02-23T11:34:06Z",
            "Survey": 24154,
            "Respondent": -1,
            "Answers": [
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184730404,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:34:06Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390002,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "Name, Vorname",
                    "AnswerText": "PD Dr. Kuckertz, Andreas",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184730405,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:34:06Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390003,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "Hochschule, Ort",
                    "AnswerText": "TU Dortmund/ Uni DuE",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184730406,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:34:06Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390004,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "E-Mail-Adresse",
                    "AnswerText": "andreas.kuckertz@icb.uni-due.de",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184730050,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:34Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390005,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "ja",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184730016,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:23Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390010,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "ja",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729987,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:15Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390013,
                    "QuestionType": "DROPDOWN",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "Sommersemester 2017",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 5,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729963,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:05Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390024,
                    "QuestionType": "CHECKBOX",
                    "QuestionText": "(Mehrfachnennung möglich)",
                    "AnswerText": "",
                    "AnswerNumeric": -1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729964,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:03Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390024,
                    "QuestionType": "CHECKBOX",
                    "QuestionText": "Master",
                    "AnswerText": "",
                    "AnswerNumeric": -1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729965,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:03Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390024,
                    "QuestionType": "CHECKBOX",
                    "QuestionText": "Diplom",
                    "AnswerText": "",
                    "AnswerNumeric": -1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729943,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:33:00Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390028,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "Anzahl:",
                    "AnswerText": "30",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729843,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:32:30Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390031,
                    "QuestionType": "TEXT_FIELD",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "Gründungsfinanzierung",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 1,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729824,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:32:18Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390032,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "ja, als eines von mehreren Lehrbüchern",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729703,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:31:34Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390037,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "gut",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                },
                {
                    "AnswerId": 184729678,
                    "Created": "2012-02-23T11:31:29Z",
                    "AnswerSet": 19509338,
                    "QuestionItem": 4390042,
                    "QuestionType": "RADIOBUTTON",
                    "QuestionText": "",
                    "AnswerText": "gut",
                    "AnswerNumeric": 2,
                    "AnswerWeight": null
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}